zp1.com 2012-12-24

# ZP1.com - Free Ads - Free Classified Ads - Free Personal Ads - American Classifieds - Post Free Ads

**You are currently viewing from Los Angeles, California

Privacy Policy

**

Your privacy is very important to us. This notice explains our online information policies and describes how the information collected at this site is used. 

**Registered User Profiles**

When you register on this site, your information is protected by the use of a password, which you select. Each person who registers must have a unique email address and username. Duplicate profiles using the same email address or username are not permitted. We highly recommend that you select a password that is neither common nor known to others. 

We encourage you to NOT use information such as your social security number, phone number or date of birth as your password. If you are already a registered user and you have lost or forgotten your password, you may only obtain it by emailing us with your full username and contact information, and we will email you your password. For your protection, we cannot provide your password by any other means. We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time, by logging into the "my account" link provided on our website. You may view and edit personal information you have already given us. You may also elect to receive or discontinue receiving any email newsletters we may choose to distribute periodically. 

Once you register, you won't need to do it again. Wherever you go on ZP1.com, your information stays with you.

**User Warnings and User Conduct**

In consideration for our services, you also agree not to: 

1\. Violate any applicable law, regulation or rule;

2\. Harass, offend, threaten, embarrass, distress or invade the privacy of any individual or entity; 

3\. Post or transmit any commercial, advertising or promotional materials, including without limitation, "spam" or mass distributions;

4\. Provide false information on your registration form, or impersonate another person at any point; 

5\. Post or transmit false, inappropriate, improper, disorderly or excessive messages or information. 

6\. Post any material that infringes upon any third party's copyright, trademark, patent or other intellectual property right. 

If you violate such terms, we may, without prior notice and without liability to you, ban you from any and all services, terminate your registration, delete your messages or postings, and take any other action we deem appropriate, at our sole discretion. You agree that we are not responsible or liable for deactivation or deletion of accounts, or for loss of emails, communications, postings, data or information as a result of, or arising out of, our administration of such services. We assume no responsibility for the accuracy, integrity, quality completeness, usefulness or value of any content, data, documents, graphics, images, information, advice, or opinion contained. 

7. You are using the site at your own risk. The content of all the information is used at your own risk. It is important when dealing with other people not to use online money transfers such as Western Union, or even PayPal. Our classifieds are meant to be used to meet people in your area and see the product before you buy it.

**Information Collected on this Site**  

Your privacy is very important to us. This notice explains our online information policies and describes how the information collected at this site is used. Web sites, the type of personally identifiable information that may be collected about you (or others for whom you submit) may include name, address, email address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of our various products and services, depending on the product or service for which you are seeking information. 

Only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products and services from the ZP1.com Web site. We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our Web pages, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows95 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online etc.). 

**How We Use the Information** ** **

1\. We may use your information to fulfill your requests for our products or services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, or to offer you additional products, programs and services that may be of interest to you. We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to fulfill a request by you. 

2\. We may use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you new products, programs or services. 

3\. We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to a legal process. For example, we may disclose personally identifiable information in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request. 

4\. Agents, employees and contractors of ZP1.com who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services which they are performing for ZP1.com. We may combine information which we receive online with information from outside records to enhance our ability to market products or services that may be of interest to you. 

5\. Finally, ZP1.com and the Web site covered by this Privacy Notice will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways which are unrelated to those described above without also providing you with an opportunity to first opt out of these unrelated uses. Collection of information by third-party sites and our sponsor's sites may contain links to other sites whose information and privacy practices may differ from ours. We do not have control over information that is submitted to, or collected by sites other than ours. You should consult with the privacy notices on those sites. The ZP1.com Web site covered by this Privacy Notice may from time to time offer content that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit in order to participate in the site activity. ZP1.com has no control over use of this information by such third parties. The ZP1.com site will notify you at such time if third parties will obtain such information.

**Our Commitment to Security**

We take reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial measures to safeguard, maintain and help prevent unauthorized access to the information that we collect online. 

**Terms & Conditions**

The materials on this Web site (the "Site") are provided by ZP1.com ("ZP1.com") as a service to its users and may be used for informational purposes only, subject to the provisions below. By downloading any materials from or otherwise using this Site, you as a user ("you") agree to these terms and conditions ("Agreement"). If you do not agree to them, do not use the Site or download any materials from it. You agree that this Agreement (and, if you are a user who has registered on this Site ("Registered User")), any provisions included in the registration process is the complete and exclusive statement of the agreement between ZP1.com and you, which supersedes any proposal or prior agreement, oral or written, and any other communications between you and ZP1.com relating to the subject matter of this Agreement. 

All information on ZP1.com, including any credit card information, is SSL Secure and Verizon secure with the highest level of security. 

ZP1.com MAY REVISE THIS AGREEMENT AT ANY TIME BY UPDATING THIS POSTING. YOU SHOULD VISIT THIS PAGE FROM TIME TO TIME TO REVIEW THE MOST CURRENT TERMS BECAUSE THEY ARE BINDING ON YOU. CERTAIN PROVISIONS OF THESE TERMS MAY BE SUPERSEDED BY EXPRESSLY DESIGNATED LEGAL NOTICES OR TERMS LOCATED ON PARTICULAR PAGES AT THIS SITE.

**TRADEMARK INFORMATION**

All brand, product, service, and process names appearing on this Site are trademarks of their respective holders. Reference to or use of a product, service, or process does not imply recommendation, approval, affiliation, or sponsorship of that product, service, or process by ZP1.com.

**OWNERSHIP OF MATERIALS**

This Site and Materials located hereon are copyrighted and are protected by worldwide copyright, trademark, trade dress and other intellectual property laws and treaty provisions, and may not be copied, reproduced, modified, published, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way, without ZP1.com's prior written permission. Except as expressly provided herein, ZP1.com and its suppliers do not grant, by implication, or otherwise, any express or implied right to you under any patents, copyrights, trademarks, or trade secret information. Other rights may be granted to you by ZP1.com in writing or incorporated elsewhere in the Materials.

**TERMINATION OF ACCESS**

ZP1.com may, at its sole discretion, (a) suspend your access to certain areas of the Site or (b) terminate your access to certain areas of the Site. Whether or not a breach of this agreement results in suspension or termination depends on several factors, including but not limited to the severity of the breach, the potential harm to other users or to ZP1.com, and whether or not the breach is repeated or cured. ZP1.com may suspend or terminate your right to access or use the site without warning or any explanation. We may also block your I.P. and ban you from access to ZP1.com. Upon termination, you will immediately destroy the Materials and any licenses herein shall immediately terminate. Any illegal products, Illegal use of the site or terrorists will be reported to the FBI.

This site does not support any spam. Anyone caught spamming on ZP1.com will have their information, including e-mail and contacts, passed on to a virtual portal robot that will spam you back the same way you spam ZP1.com. We reserve the right to spam anyone that spams us. Please use the Web site responsibly.

Thank you for visiting ZP1.com. We hope you find value on our site.
